🎵 하나님의 은혜 (나를 지으신 이가 하나님) - 찬양 전주
Grace of God - Park Jong-ho (Intro)
[1절] 나를 지으신 이가 하나님, 나를 부르신 이가 하나님
The One who made me is God, The One who called me is God
나를 보내신 이도 하나님, 나의 달려갈 길 다 가도록
The One who sent me is also God, That I may run my entire race
나의 마지막 호흡 다하도록, 나로 그 십자가 품게 하시니
Until my very last breath, Letting me embrace that cross
나의 달려갈 길 다 가도록, 나의 마지막 호흡 다하도록
That I may run my entire race, until my very last breath
[후렴] 한량없는 은혜, 갚을 길 없는 은혜
Boundless grace, grace that cannot be repaid
내 삶을 에워싸는 하나님의 은혜
God's grace that surrounds my life
나 주저함 없이 그 땅을 밟음도
That I walk upon that land without hesitation
나를 붙드시는 하나님의 은혜
Is the grace of God that holds me fast
(간주)
(Interlude)
[2절] 나를 지으신 이가 하나님, 나를 부르신 이가 하나님
The One who made me is God, The One who called me is God
나를 보내신 이도 하나님, 나의 달려갈 길 다 가도록
The One who sent me is also God, That I may run my entire race
나의 마지막 호흡 다하도록, 나로 그 십자가 품게 하시니
Until my very last breath, Letting me embrace that cross
나의 달려갈 길 다 가도록, 나의 마지막 호흡 다하도록
That I may run my entire race, until my very last breath
[후렴] 한량없는 은혜, 갚을 길 없는 은혜
Boundless grace, grace that cannot be repaid
내 삶을 에워싸는 하나님의 은혜
God's grace that surrounds my life
나 주저함 없이 그 땅을 밟음도
That I walk upon that land without hesitation
나를 붙드시는 하나님의 은혜!
Is the grace of God that holds me fast!
[후렴 절정] 내 삶을 에워싸는 크신 은혜, 오직 하나님의 은혜라
Surrounded by God's abundant grace, only by God's grace
🕊️ 나의 모든 삶을 붙드시는 하나님의 은혜에 감사드립니다 · 아멘
Praising God's Unfailing Grace in My Entire Life · Amen